Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 83, Folder: 18 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Item 23: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.32 (1923:June 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.33 (1923:July 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.34 (1923:July 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.35 (1923:July 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.36 (1923:July 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.37 (1923:Aug. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.38 (1923:Aug. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.39 (1923:Aug. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.40 (1923:Aug. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.41 (1923:Aug. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.42 (1923:Sep. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.43 (1923:Sep. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.44 (1923:Sep. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Weekly Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    no.45 (1923:Sep. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: National Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    v.1:no.46 (1923:Oct. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: National Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    v.1:no.47 (1923:Oct. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: National Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    v.1:no.48 (1923:Nov. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: National Bulletin, Publication (Box 83, Folder 18)
    v.1:no.49 (1923:Nov. 26). Item is in English.
- Box: 83, Folder: 19 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Advance Copy of the Report of Committee on Employment, Publication (Box 83, Folder 19)
    By The National Association of Corporation Schools. Eight Annual Convention. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Advance Copy of the Report of Committee on Employment Plans, Publication (Box 83, Folder 19)
    By The National Association of Corporation Schools. Fifth Annual Convention; Buffalo, New York. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Advance Copy of the Report of Committee on Unskilled Labor and Americanization, Publication (Box 83, Folder 19)
    By The National Association of Corporation Schools. Ninth Annual Convention; Niagara Falls, N.Y. Item is in English.
- Box: 84, Folder: 1 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: How the Cotton Industry Has Safeguarded its Employees, Publication (Box 84, Folder 1)
    By George V. S. Michaels. Address before the National Association of Cotton Manufacturers Ninetieth Meeting, April 13, 1911. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Some Labor Problems, Publication (Box 84, Folder 1)
    By Charles G. Bancroft. Address before the National Association of Cotton Manufacturers, September 10, 1915. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Report of Study of labor Agreements in 72 Northern Cotton and Rayon Textile Mills, Publication (Box 84, Folder 1)
    By James A. Irvine; Helen F. Callahan. June 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 84, Folder: 2 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Bylaws of the National Association of Educational Negotiators, Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
    By National Association of Educational Negotiators. Item is in English.
- Box: 84, Folder: 3 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Electrical Construction Industry in the United States and Canada Its Origin, Function and Purpose, Publication (Box 84, Folder 3)
    By Council on Industrial Relations for the Electrical Construction Industry. Item is in English.
- Box: 84, Folder: 4 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Relationships and Adjustments between Employer and Employed, Publication (Box 84, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Employment Managers. Minutes of the Second Bi-Monthly Conference National Association Employment Managers. Item is in English.
- Box: 84, Folder: 5 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: My Future is with the management teamunited in a common effort!, Publication (Box 84, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Foremen. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The FOREMEN'S Magazine, Publication (Box 84, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Foremen. v.2:no.3 (1926:May). Item is in English.
- Box: 84, Folder: 6 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of the National Association of the Fur Industry, Publication (Box 84, Folder 6)
    By National Association of the Fur Industry. Headquarters New York City, NY. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Fur Industry, Publication (Box 84, Folder 6)
    By David C. Mills. Reprinted from Journal of Home Economics. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Dictionary of Fur Names, Publication (Box 84, Folder 6)
    By Bridgewater M. Arnold. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Dictionary of Fur Names, Publication (Box 84, Folder 6)
    By Horace J. McMullen. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Letter to the Governors and Members, Publication (Box 84, Folder 6)
    By David C. Mills. August 16, 1928. Item is in English.
- Box: 84, Folder: 7 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Labor Unions and the Furniture Industry, Publication (Box 84, Folder 7)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Address before the Annual Meeting, September 30, 1928. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Monthly Statistical Report October 1961, Publication (Box 84, Folder 7)
    By John M. Snow. Item is in English.
- Box: 84, Folder: 8 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: December Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.61-125 (1961:Dec. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Monthly Statistical Report January 1962, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: January Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-9 (1962:Jan. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Monthly Statistical Report February 1962, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: February Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-20 (1962:Feb. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: March Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-35 (1962:Mar. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: April Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-47 (1962:Apr. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Monthly Statistical Report April 1962, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: May Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-59 (1962:May 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Monthly Statistical Report May 1962, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: June Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-63 (1962:June 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Monthly Statistical Report June 1962, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: July Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-69 (1962:July 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Monthly Statistical Report July 1962, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: News From NAM, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. August 8, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: August Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-70 (1962:Aug. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Monthly Statistical Report August 1962, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Monthly Statistical Report September 1962, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Memorandum To: Upholstered Furniture Manufacturers, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Furniture Manufacturers. October 12, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: October Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-86 (1962:Oct. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: For Sale: Electric Switches and Boxes, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.62-86 (1962:Oct. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Sales Executive Available, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.62-88 (1962:Oct. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Factory Executive Available, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.62-89 (1962:Oct. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Upholstery Frame Plant Available, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.62-90 (1962:Oct. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Upholstery Frame Plant Available, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.62-90 (1962:Oct. 31). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Applicant for Employment, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.62-91 (1962:Oct. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Equipment for Sale, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.62-95 (1962:Nov. 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: November Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-97 (1962:Nov. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Monthly Statistical Report November 1962, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 30: December Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.62-105 (1962:Dec. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Monthly Statistical Report December 1962, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 32: January Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.63-7 (1963:Jan. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Monthly Statistical Report January 1963, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 34: February Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.63-14 (1963:Feb. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Monthly Statistical Report February 1963, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 36: March Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.63-21 (1963:Mar. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Monthly Statistical Report March 1963, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 38: April Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.63-29 (1963:Apr. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: May Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.63-34 (1963:May 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: July Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.63-43 (1963:July 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: August Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.63-51 (1963:Aug. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Monthly Statistical Report August 1963, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 43: Product Control Supervisor Available, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.63-57 (1963:Sep. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: September Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.63-59 (1963:Sep. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Monthly Statistical Report September 1963, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 46: October Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.63-64 (1963:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Monthly Statistical Report October 1963, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 48: November Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Lynn W. Beman. Bulletin no.63-73 (1963:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Monthly Statistical Report November 1963, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 50: December Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Furniture Manufacturers. Bulletin no.63-76 (1963:Dec. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Monthly Statistical Report December 1963, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 52: January Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Furniture Manufacturers. Bulletin no.64-5 (1964:Jan. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: March Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Furniture Manufacturers. Bulletin no.64-15 (1964:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Monthly Statistical Report March 1964, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 55: Monthly Statistical Report April 1964, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 56: July Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.64-43 (1964:July 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Monthly Statistical Report July 1964, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 58: August Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.64-50 (1964:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Monthly Statistical Report August 1964, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 60: Sales Management vs. Production Management, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. August 11, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: September Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.64-54 (1964:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Monthly Statistical Report September 1964, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 63: October Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.64-62 (1964:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Monthly Statistical Report October 1964, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 65: November Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.64-65 (1964:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Monthly Statistical Report November 1964, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 67: December Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.64-74 (1964:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Monthly Statistical Report December 1964, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 69: January Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.65-5 (1965:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Monthly Statistical Report January 1965, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 71: February Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.65-12 (1965:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 72: Monthly Statistical Report February 1965, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 73: March Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.65-19 (1965:Apr. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 74: Monthly Statistical Report March 1965, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 75: April Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.65-25 (1965:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Monthly Statistical Report April 1965, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 77: May Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.65-27 (1965:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 78: Monthly Statistical Report May 1965, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 79: Dear Member, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. June 8, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 80: Export Trade Opportunity, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.65-28 (1965:June 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 81: Monthly Statistical Report June 1965, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 82: manufacturers Shipments of Household Furniture, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Furniture Manufacturers. June, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 83: July Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.65-30 (1965:July 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 84: Monthly Statistical Report July 1965, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 85: Wanted: Juvenile Furniture Manufacturer, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.65-31 (1965:July 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 86: Report on the Nigerian Wooden Furniture Industry Cites Opportunies for Investors, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Furniture Manufacturers. Bulletin no.65-32 (1965:July 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 87: State Taxation Report Completed, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Furniture Manufacturers. Bulletin no.65-33 (1965:July 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 88: August Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.65-37 (1965:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 89: Monthly Statistical Report August 1965, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 90: Monthly Statistical Report September 1965, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 91: Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.65-45 (1965:Dec. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 92: Kuwait to Buy Furniture for New Hilton Hotel, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.65-46 (1965:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 93: Wood Parts Wanted, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.65-47 (1965:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 94: Machinery Wanted, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By John M. Snow. Bulletin no.65-48 (1965:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 95: Monthly Statistical Report December 1965, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Item 96: December Labor Relations Report, Publication (Box 84, Folder 8)
    By Bernard A. Riemer. Bulletin no.65-51 (1965:Dec. 31). Item is in English.
- Box: 84, Folder: 9 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: What Should be the Role of Government in Research, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Panel--Economic Outlook and What to Do About It, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By H. B. Arthur. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Fighting Inflation: A Two Front Challenge, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Lewis H. Brown. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Industry's Answer to the Police State, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Earl Bunting. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Costs v. Benefits in Government Spending, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Harry F. Byrd. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Peaceful Settlement of Disputes, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Cyrus S. Ching. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: On Guard for Freedom, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By F. C. Crawford. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Administering the Labor-Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Robert N. Denham. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Challenge From Abroad, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Allen Welsh Dulles. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Role of Government in Research, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Gustov Egloff. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Causes of Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Clarence Francis. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Fight For Men's Minds, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Robert I. Gannon. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Panel--Economic Outlook and What to Do About It, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By William H. Grimes. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Keeping Our Powder Dry, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Thomas J. Hargrave. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Panel--Economic Outlook and What to Do About It, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Henry Hazlitt. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Tailoring the Budget to the Nation's Needs, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Thomas S. Holden. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Tailoring the Budget to the Nation's Needs, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Thomas S. Holden. December 5,1947. Copty 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Address to Patents and Industrial Research session, Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Dr. Robert M. Hutchins. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Legislative Outlook, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Joseph W. Martin. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Call To Action On Taxes, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Don G. Mitchell. December, 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Address to Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Stanislaw Mikolajczyk. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Building on Faith, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Holcombe Parkes. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Address to Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Clarence B. Randall. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Address to Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Clarence B. Randall. December 3, 1947. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: New Issues in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Frank Rising. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Address to Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Morris Sayre. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Capital Needs of an Expanding Economy, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Murray Shields. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Address to Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Raymond S. Smethurst. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Benefits Versus Costs in Federal Government Spending, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By John J. Sparkman. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Communist Influence in Labor Unions, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By H. W. Story. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Industry's Stake in International Issues, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By J. R. Suman. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: What the Public Expects of Management and Labor, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By George W. Taylor. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Economic Output and What to Do About It, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Alan Temple. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Freedom and Prices, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Robert R. Wason. December 2, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Patents and Progress, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Alexander Wiley. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Let's Stay Free, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Charles E. Wilson. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Let's Stay Free, Publication (Box 84, Folder 9)
    By Charles E. Wilson. December 5, 1947. Condensed version. Item is in English.
- Box: 84, Folder: 10 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Check List for Strengthening Management Teamwork, Publication (Box 84, Folder 10)
    October, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Personnel Organization and Administration, Publication (Box 84, Folder 10)
    By Howard Dirks. January 6-10, 1947. Item is in English.